http://www.moneyshow.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. The following is the privacy policy of MoneyShow.com and MoneyShow regarding the use of personal information collected on MoneyShow.com and on MoneyShow's affiliated conference Web sites.
Users are not required to provide any personal information to access some free sections of MoneyShow.com and MoneyShow's conference Web sites. However, for full access to MoneyShow.com and all of its contents, or to receive one of our newsletters by e-mail, or offers from MoneyShow.com partners, it will be necessary to provide some basic information about yourself such as your name, e-mail address, as well as other personal information. You will then also be asked to create a username and password for future access to MoneyShow.com.
If you purchase something through MoneyShow.com or MoneyShow's affiliated conference Web sites, you will also be asked to provide credit card and other information. To preserve a secure environment, we use standard 128 bit encryption technology, authentication, and other measures to protect your data (assuming your browser is equipped with this encryption technology).
We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in place to protect personal information about you. Nevertheless, although we use these techniques to protect your privacy, we do not promise nor should you expect that your personal information or private communications will always remain private in an online environment.
MoneyShow and its agents or service providers or business partners may receive and store certain information automatically when you visit our Sites (MoneyShow.com and MoneyShow's affiliated conference and eShow websites). This may include information on your browser type and operating system, the pages that you view, referring sites (sites you visited before you came to our site and sites you go to after you visit our site), IP addresses, or unique device identifiers associated with mobile devices, smart phones, etc. This information allows us to count the total number of "hits" on our Sites. We collect certain information using technology, like cookies and pixel tags.
Third party analytics and advertising networks also use cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, clear GIFs and other technology to collect certain information automatically. Advertising networks may use this information to serve you targeted ads, on this site and other sites, for products and services that, based on your activities, are likely to be of interest to you ("interest-based advertising").
Outside companies' advertisements may be displayed on our Web site, and these companies may set cookies on your computer. The use of these are subject to each company's own privacy policy, and not ours.
A "cookie" is a small file that does not contain personally identifiable information and is saved on your computer or mobile device. Cookies help improve your user experience, and allow us to analyze our Sites and manage the advertising that is served to you.
Our cookies help to give you faster access to pages you have already visited; they allow you to personalize your pages and us to customize our offerings; and they help you to participate in some activities or events on our Sites.
We also use cookies to help us figure out how many people visit our Sites, which of our Web pages they go to and how long they stay there. This information helps us figure out which of our Web features are successes and what Sites might need improvement. You can set your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent or turn off all cookies through your Internet browser (e.g., Internet Explorer or Safari). Check your browser's Help menu or your built-in mobile device settings to find out how. Some mobile devices store cookies not only in areas connected to the browser, but also in areas that are app-specific so these cookies cannot be controlled by the browser settings. Check your app settings options on your mobile device to find out how to manage or delete cookies that may be stored in these other areas.
Please note that if you do not accept cookies, some features or activities may not be available to you.
To learn more about cookies and how you can control their use, visit these sites:Google's Ad Settings - http://www.google.com/settings/adsGoogle's Policies & Principles about cookies - http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/The Network Advertising Initiative - http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp
Anonymous information about our users in aggregate, such as a user's status as an investor or professional advisor, or other information you may provide as part of the registration process, may be provided to our advertisers and business partners so that appropriate advertisements can be displayed.
Your personal information will not be sold or shared with any company not affiliated with MoneyShow.com or MoneyShow, without your permission, with the following exceptions:
In response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process from law enforcement agencies or to defend against legal claims;
We provide information to investigate or prevent suspected illegal activities.
For users based outside the United States who register for membership on this site, please note that the personal information you provided as part of your registration will be processed and stored in the US and, therefore, may be accessible to law enforcement and national security authorities in that jurisdiction.
MoneyShow endeavors to comply with the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation, or GDPR, by providing clear and conspicuous opt-in language when users sign up for events, or request to receive information or services from us. For EU citizens we will be responsive to requests to review, make changes or delete the data that we store on those individuals. If you need to review personally identifiable data we have stored for you, please send an email with a complete explanation of your request, along with your name and physical mailing address to customerservice@moneyshow.com.
With your permission (through our "opt-in" messages on registration or special offers pages of this site) we may send you e-mail messages such as service announcements and other event related messages, as well as our newsletter, and special offers from our partners that you may choose to receive, but you will maintain the right to change your "opt-in" status going forward through online communications and/or other means through this Web site.
CHANGES TO THIS POLICY: If our policy changes, we will post the new policy on the Web site and changes will be made applicable within 24 hours. Please check back often to review the latest changes.
How to contact us about privacy issues: by mail, send correspondence to: Customer Service, MoneyShow.com or MoneyShow, 50 Central Avenue, Suite 980, Sarasota, FL 34236. By e-mail send inquiries to: customerservice@moneyshow.com.
Last updated: May 25, 2018
Upcoming Events
MoneyShow January Virtual Expo
January 12 - 14, 2021
FOCUS:
Strategies
The Accredited Investors Virtual Expo
January 26 - 28, 2021
FOCUS:
Accredited Investors
Featured Partners
Learn More
Uncommon
Uncommon Giving Corporation, The Generosity Company™, is a pre-IPO, for-profit business focused on a...
Wildcat Exploration LLC
Wildcat Exploration, LLC is a small, family-owned oil company. Wildcat Exploration designs projects ...
Amex Exploration
Amex Exploration has made a significant high-grade gold discovery on its 100% owned project in Perro...
High Dividend Opportunities
High Dividend Opportunities is the largest community of income investors and retirees with 4000+ mem...
See All MoneyShow Partners
